http://www.brilliantsign.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for http://www.brilliantsign.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it isused and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collectinformation that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sellor rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We willnot share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than asnecessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials,new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any timeby contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via thewebsite, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encryptedand transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the addressbar and looking for &quot;https&quot; at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect yourinformation offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (forexample, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secureenvironment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact usimmediately via telephone at (216) 741-3800 or on our contact page.
